const data = [
    {
      question: "Why are clearly defined quality assurance standards/protocol important in the gathering of lake data?",
      options: [
        "To ensure uniformity in the process of gathering data.",
        "To ensure that data results are comparable with past and future data.",
        "To be able to provide all users of LSM data gathered by trained volunteers of the accuracy and credibility of the information.",
        "All of the above."
      ],
      correct_option: ["All of the above."]
    },
    {
      question: "Who can submit lake water quality data gathered on Maine lakes to LSM and the Maine Department of Environmental Protection (DEP)?",
      options: [
        "Anyone who has a background in lake biology.",
        "Only individuals who are willing to spend time in the water gathering samples.",
        "Individuals who have received standardized training by LSM or Maine DEP staff, and who have met all required certification standards."
      ],
      correct_option: ["Individuals who have received standardized training by LSM or Maine DEP staff, and who have met all required certification standards."]
    },
    {
      question: "How does Secchi disk data gathered by properly trained and certified volunteers compare to similar data gathered by professionals?",
      options: [
        "Providing that the individuals have met all quality assurance and certification standards, there should be little or no difference between the two.",
        "Typically, the professional data are of higher quality.",
        "Volunteer data cannot be compared to that gathered by professional lake scientists."
      ],
      correct_option: ["Providing that the individuals have met all quality assurance and certification standards, there should be little or no difference between the two."]
    },
    {
      question: "What is the best way to enter data legibly on the official data sheets provided by LSM?",
      options: [
        "Use a notebook or pad to record the data when you are out on the water, and transfer the information to the official data form at another convenient time.",
        "Data should always be entered directly on the field sheet/form while working on the water, and should not be transferred to the form from another source.",
        "Write it on your hand and transcribe it back onto the sheet when back home.",
        "Log it on the meter if you have that capability."
      ],
      correct_option: ["Data should always be entered directly on the field sheet/form while working on the water, and should not be transferred to the form from another source."]
    },
    {
      question: "What time of day should Secchi readings be taken?",
      options: [
        "At any convenient time from one hour after sunrise, to one hour prior to sunset.",
        "Ideally between 9AM and 3PM.",
        "Only at a time when the sky is free of cloud cover.",
        "At a time when there is no wind and the lake is calm."
      ],
      correct_option: ["Ideally between 9AM and 3PM."]
    },
    {
      question: "Where should Secchi readings be taken?",
      options: [
        "Anywhere the lake is sufficiently deep to ensure that the disk will not hit bottom while it is still visible.",
        "Readings should always be taken as close to the middle of the lake as possible.",
        "At designated (by MDEP/LSM) monitoring locations/stations, as indicated on a bathymetric map provide through LSM, DEP, or the www.lakesofmaine.org website."
      ],
      correct_option:  ["At designated (by MDEP/LSM) monitoring locations/stations, as indicated on a bathymetric map provide through LSM, DEP, or the www.lakesofmaine.org website."]
    },
    {
      question: "How can you determine whether or not you are at the designated monitoring station?",
      options: [
        "a. Through the use of a GPS device, using coordinates that are available for the location of the monitoring station on your lake.",
        "b. By “triangulating” the location using shoreline, adjacent terrain reference points.",
        "c. Through memory and guesswork.",
        "a or b, providing that you are able to verify the depth, once you have arrived."
      ],
      correct_option: ["a or b, providing that you are able to verify the depth, once you have arrived."]
    },
    {
      question: "How often should you take and record a second quality assurance Secchi disk reading during the annual monitoring period?",
      options: [
        "Not at all, unless you have taken at least 10 readings.",
        "At least one second reading during the season, two if you take between 11 and 20 original readings at a sampling station.",
        "Only once during the season, regardless of the total number of readings that you take."
      ],
      correct_option:[ "At least one second reading during the season, two if you take between 11 and 20 original readings at a sampling station."]
    },
    {
      question: "How close in time to the original reading should the quality assurance duplicate reading be taken?",
      options: [
        "Within the few minutes of the original reading.",
        "Within 24 hours of the original reading.",
        "Any time during the day of the original reading."
      ],
      correct_option: ["Within the few minutes of the original reading."]
    },
    {
      question: "When is it necessary to anchor the boat when taking a Secchi reading?",
      options: [
        "Only if the wind speed exceeds 3-5 mph.",
        "Always.",
        "Only if you think that the boat is drifting away from the designated monitoring station."
      ],
      correct_option: ["Always."]
    }
  ];

  export default data
  